Guide to the Gay U.S.A. Collection MSS.426
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Video recordings, 2000-2012
  - Gay USA 8/20/2009, August 20, 2009; ID: 426.0363; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0363)
  - Gay USA 8/27/2009, August 27, 2009; ID: 426.0364; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0364)
  - Gay USA 9/3/2009, September 3, 2009; ID: 426.0365; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0365)
  - Gay USA 9/10/2009, September 10, 2009; ID: 426.0366; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0366)
  - Gay USA 9/17/2009, September 17, 2009; ID: 426.0367; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0367)
  - Gay USA 9/24/2009 - Lee Badgett, September 24, 2009; ID: 426.0368; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0368)
  - Gay USA 10/1/2009, October 1, 2009; ID: 426.0369; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0369)
  - Gay USA 10/15/2009 - Coleman Domingo, October 15, 2009; ID: 426.0370; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0370)
  - Gay USA 10/22/2009, October 22, 2009; ID: 426.0371; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0371)
  - Gay USA 10/29/2009, October 29, 2009; ID: 426.0372; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0372)
  - Gay USA 11/5/2009 - Sarah Schulman, November 5, 2009; ID: 426.0373; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0373)
  - Gay USA 11/12/2009, November 12, 2009; ID: 426.0374; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0374)
  - Gay USA 11/19/2009 - Bishop Gene Robinson, November 19, 2009; ID: 426.0375; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0375)
  - Gay USA 11/26/2009, November 26, 2009; ID: 426.0376; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0376)
  - Gay USA 12/3/2009, December 3, 2009; ID: 426.0377; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0377)
  - Gay USA 12/10/2009, December 10, 2009; ID: 426.0378; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0378)
  - Gay USA 12/17/2009, December 17, 2009; ID: 426.0379; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0379)
  - Gay USA 12/24/2009, December 24, 2009; ID: 426.0380; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0380)
  - Gay USA 12/31/2009, December 31, 2009; ID: 426.0381; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0381)
  - Gay USA 1/7/2010, January 7, 2010; ID: 426.0382; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0382)
  - Gay USA 1/14/2010, January 14, 2010; ID: 426.0383; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0383)
  - Gay USA 1/21/2010, January 21, 2010; ID: 426.0384; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0384)
  - Gay USA 1/28/2010, January 28, 2010; ID: 426.0385; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0385)
  - Gay USA 2/4/2010, February 4, 2010; ID: 426.0386; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0386)
  - Gay USA 2/11/2010, February 11, 2010; ID: 426.0387; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0387)
  - Gay USA 2/18/2010, February 18, 2010; ID: 426.0388; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0388)
  - Gay USA 2/23/2010, February 23, 2010; ID: 426.0389; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0389)
  - Gay USA 3/4/2010, March 4, 2010; ID: 426.0390; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0390)
  - Gay USA 3/11/2010, March 11, 2010; ID: 426.0391; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0391)
  - Gay USA 3/18/2010, March 18, 2010; ID: 426.0392; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0392)
  - Gay USA 3/25/2010, March 25, 2010; ID: 426.0393; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0393)
  - Gay USA 4/1/2010, April 1, 2010; ID: 426.0394; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0394)
  - Gay USA 4/8/2010, April 8, 2010; ID: 426.0395; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0395)
  - Gay USA 4/15/2010, April 15, 2010; ID: 426.0396; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0396)
  - Gay USA 4/22/2010, April 22, 2010; ID: 426.0397; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0397)
  - Gay USA 4/29/2010, April 29, 2010; ID: 426.0398; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0398)
  - Gay USA 5/6/2010, May 6, 2010; ID: 426.0399; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0399)
  - Gay USA 5/13/2010, May 13, 2010; ID: 426.0400; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0400)
  - Gay USA 5/20/2010, May 20, 2010; ID: 426.0401; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0401)
  - Gay USA 5/27/2010, May 27, 2010; ID: 426.0402; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0402)
  - Gay USA 6/3/2010, June 3, 2010; ID: 426.0403; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0403)
  - Gay USA 6/10/2010, June 10, 2010; ID: 426.0404; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0404)
  - Gay USA 6/17/2010, June 17, 2010; ID: 426.0405; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0405)
  - Gay USA 6/24/2010, June 24, 2010; ID: 426.0406; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0406)
  - Gay USA 7/1/2010, July 1, 2010; ID: 426.0407; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0407)
  - Gay USA 7/8/2010, July 8, 2010; ID: 426.0408; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0408)
  - Gay USA 7/15/2010, July 15, 2010; ID: 426.0409; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0409)
  - Gay USA 7/22/2010, July 22, 2010; ID: 426.0410; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0410)
  - Gay USA 7/29/2010, July 29, 2010; ID: 426.0411; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0411)
  - Gay USA 8/5/2010, July 5, 2010; ID: 426.0412; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0412)
  - Gay USA 8/12/2010, August 12, 2010; ID: 426.0413; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0413)
  - Gay USA 8/19/2010, August 19, 2010; ID: 426.0414; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0414)
  - Gay USA 8/26/2010, August 26, 2010; ID: 426.0415; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0415)
  - Gay USA 9/2/2010, September 2, 2010; ID: 426.0416; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0416)
  - Gay USA 9/9/2010, September 9, 2010; ID: 426.0417; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0417)
  - Gay USA 9/16/2010, September 16, 2010; ID: 426.0418; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0418)
  - Gay USA 9/23/2010, September 23, 2010; ID: 426.0419; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0419)
  - Gay USA 9/30/2010, September 30, 2010; ID: 426.0420; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0420)
  - Gay USA 10/7/2010, October 7, 2010; ID: 426.0421; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0421)
  - Gay USA 10/14/2010, October 14, 2010; ID: 426.0422; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0422)
  - Gay USA 10/21/2010, October 21, 2010; ID: 426.0423; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0423)
  - Gay USA 10/28/2010, October 28, 2010; ID: 426.0424; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0424)
  - Gay USA 11/4/2010, November 4, 2010; ID: 426.0425; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0425)
  - Gay USA 11/11/2010, November 11, 2010; ID: 426.0426; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0426)
  - Gay USA 11/18/2010, November 18, 2010; ID: 426.0427; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0427)
  - Gay USA 11/25/2010, November 25, 2010; ID: 426.0428; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0428)
  - Gay USA 12/2/2010, December 2, 2010; ID: 426.0429; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 7, Media ID: 426.0429)
  - Gay USA 12/9/2010, December 9, 2010; ID: 426.0430; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0430)
  - Gay USA 12/16/2010, December 16, 2010; ID: 426.0431; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0431)
  - Gay USA 12/23/2010, December 23, 2010; ID: 426.0432; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0432)
  - Gay USA 12/30/2010, December 30, 2010; ID: 426.0433; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0433)
  - Gay USA 1/6/2011, January 6, 2011; ID: 426.0434; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0434)
  - Gay USA 1/13/2011, January 13, 2011; ID: 426.0435; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0435)
  - Gay USA 1/20/2011, January 20, 2011; ID: 426.0436; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0436)
  - Gay USA 1/27/2011, January 27, 2011; ID: 426.0437; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0437)
  - Gay USA 2/3/2011, February 3, 2011; ID: 426.0438; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0438)
  - Gay USA 2/10/2011, February 10, 2011; ID: 426.0439; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0439)
  - Gay USA 2/17/2011, February 17, 2011; ID: 426.0440; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0440)
  - Gay USA 2/24/2011, February 24, 2011; ID: 426.0441; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0441)
  - Gay USA 3/3/2011, March 3, 2011; ID: 426.0442; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0442)
  - Gay USA 3/10/2011, March 10, 2011; ID: 426.0443; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0443)
  - Gay USA 3/17/2011, March 17, 2011; ID: 426.0444; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0444)
  - Gay USA 3/24/2011, March 24, 2011; ID: 426.0445; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0445)
  - Gay USA 3/31/2011, March 31, 2011; ID: 426.0446; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0446)
  - Gay USA 4/7/2011, April 7, 2011; ID: 426.0447; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0447)
  - Gay USA 4/14/2011, April 14, 2011; ID: 426.0448; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0448)
  - Gay USA 4/21/2011, April 21, 2011; ID: 426.0449; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0449)
  - Gay USA 4/28/2011, April 28, 2011; ID: 426.0450; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0450)
  - Gay USA 5/5/2011, May 5, 2011; ID: 426.0451; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0451)
  - Gay USA 5/11/2011, May 11, 2011; ID: 426.0452; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0452)
  - Gay USA 5/19/2011, May 19, 2011; ID: 426.0453; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0453)
  - Gay USA 5/26/2011, May 26, 2011; ID: 426.0454; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0454)
  - Gay USA 6/2/2011, June 2, 2011; ID: 426.0455; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0455)
  - Gay USA 6/9/2011, June 9, 2011; ID: 426.0456; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0456)
  - Gay USA 6/16/2011, June 16, 2011; ID: 426.0457; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0457)
  - Gay USA 6/23/2011, June 23, 2011; ID: 426.0458; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0458)
  - Gay USA 6/30/2011, June 30, 2011; ID: 426.0459; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0459)
  - Gay USA 7/7/2011, July 7, 2011; ID: 426.0460; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0460)
  - Gay USA 7/14/2011, July 14, 2011; ID: 426.0461; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0461)
  - Gay USA 7/21/2011, July 21, 2011; ID: 426.0462; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0462)
  - Gay USA 7/28/2011, July 28, 2011; ID: 426.0463; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0463)
  - Gay USA 8/4/2011, August 4, 2011; ID: 426.0464; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0464)
  - Gay USA 8/11/2011 - Peter Tatchell Interview, August 11, 2011; ID: 426.0465; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0465)
  - Gay USA 8/18/2011, August 18, 2011; ID: 426.0466; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0466)
  - Gay USA 8/25/2011, August 25, 2011; ID: 426.0467; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0467)
  - Gay USA 9/1/2011, September 1, 2011; ID: 426.0468; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0468)
  - Gay USA 9/8/2011, September 8, 2011; ID: 426.0469; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0469)
  - Gay USA 9/15/2011, September 15, 2011; ID: 426.0470; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0470)
  - Gay USA 9/22/2011, September 22, 2011; ID: 426.0471; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0471)
  - Gay USA 9/29/2011, September 29, 2011; ID: 426.0472; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0472)
  - Gay USA 10/6/2011, October 6, 2011; ID: 426.0473; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0473)
  - Gay USA 10/13/2011, October 13, 2011; ID: 426.0474; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0474)
  - Gay USA 10/20/2011, October 20, 2011; ID: 426.0475; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0475)
  - Gay USA 10/28/2011, October 28, 2011; ID: 426.0476; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0476)
  - Gay USA 11/3/2011, November 3, 2011; ID: 426.0477; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0477)
  - Gay USA 11/10/2011, November 10, 2011; ID: 426.0478; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0478)
  - Gay USA 11/18/2011, November 18, 2011; ID: 426.0479; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0479)
  - Gay USA 11/24/2011, November 24, 2011; ID: 426.0480; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0480)
  - Gay USA 12/01/2011, December 1, 2011; ID: 426.0481; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0481)
  - Gay USA 12/8/2011, December 8, 2011; ID: 426.0482; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0482)
  - Gay USA 12/15/2011, December 15, 2011; ID: 426.0483; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0483)
  - Gay USA 12/22/2011, December 22, 2011; ID: 426.0484; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0484)
  - Gay USA 12/29/2011, December 29, 2011; ID: 426.0485; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0485)
  - Gay USA 1/5/2012, January 5, 2012; ID: 426.0486; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0486)
  - Gay USA 1/12/2012, January 12, 2012; ID: 426.0487; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0487)
  - Gay USA 1/19/2012, January 19, 2012; ID: 426.0488; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0488)
  - Gay USA 1/26/2012, January 26, 2012; ID: 426.0489; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0489)
  - Gay USA 2/2/2012, February 2, 2012; ID: 426.0490; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 8, Media ID: 426.0490)
  - Gay USA 2/9/2012, February 9, 2012; ID: 426.0491; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0491)
  - Gay USA 2/16/2012, February 16, 2012; ID: 426.0492; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0492)
  - Gay USA 2/23/2012, February 23, 2012; ID: 426.0493; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0493)
  - Gay USA 3/1/2012, March 1, 2012; ID: 426.0494; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0494)
  - Gay USA 3/8/2012, March 8, 2012; ID: 426.0495; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0495)
  - Gay USA 3/15/2012, March 15, 2012; ID: 426.0496; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0496)
  - Gay USA 3/22/2012, March 22, 2012; ID: 426.0497; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0497)
  - Gay USA 3/27/2012, March 17, 2012; ID: 426.0498; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0498)
  - Gay USA 4/5/2012, April 5, 2012; ID: 426.0499; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0499)
  - Gay USA 4/12/2012, April 12, 2012; ID: 426.0500; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0500)
  - Gay USA 4/19/2012, April 19, 2012; ID: 426.0501; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0501)
  - Gay USA 4/26/2012, April 26, 2012; ID: 426.0502; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0502)
  - Gay USA 5/3/2012, May 3, 2012; ID: 426.0503; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0503)
  - Gay USA 5/10/2012, May 10, 2012; ID: 426.0504; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0504)
  - Gay USA 5/17/2012, May 17, 2012; ID: 426.0505; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0505)
  - Gay USA 5/24/2012, May 24, 2012; ID: 426.0506; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0506)
  - Gay USA 5/31/2012, May 31, 2012; ID: 426.0507; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0507)
  - Gay USA 6/7/2012, June 7, 2012; ID: 426.0508; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0508)
  - Gay USA 6/14/2012, June 14, 2012; ID: 426.0509; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0509)
  - Gay USA 6/21/2012, June 21, 2012; ID: 426.0510; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0510)
  - Gay USA 6/28/2012, June 28, 2012; ID: 426.0511; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0511)
  - Gay USA 7/5/2012, July 5, 2012; ID: 426.0512; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0512)
  - Gay USA 7/12/2012, July 12, 2012; ID: 426.0513; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0513)
  - Gay USA 7/19/2012, July 19, 2012; ID: 426.0514; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0514)
  - Gay USA 7/26/2012, July 26, 2012; ID: 426.0515; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0515)
  - Gay USA 8/2/2012, August 2, 2012; ID: 426.0516; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0516)
  - Gay USA 8/16/2012, August 16, 2012; ID: 426.0517; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0517)
  - Gay USA 8/9/2012, August 9, 2012; ID: 426.0518; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0518)
  - Gay USA 8/23/2012, August 23, 2012; ID: 426.0519; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0519)
  - Gay USA 8/30/2012, August 30, 2012; ID: 426.0520; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0520)
  - Gay USA 9/6/2012, September 6, 2012; ID: 426.0521; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0521)
  - Gay USA 9/13/2012, September 13, 2012; ID: 426.0522; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0522)
  - Gay USA 9/20/2012, September 20, 2012; ID: 426.0523; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0523)
  - Gay USA 9/27/2012, September 27, 2012; ID: 426.0524; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0524)
  - Gay USA 10/4/2012, October 4, 2012; ID: 426.0525; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0525)
  - Gay USA 10/11/2012, October 11, 2012; ID: 426.0526; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0526)
  - Gay USA 10/18/2012, October 18, 2012; ID: 426.0527; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0527)
  - Gay USA 10/25/2012, October 25, 2012; ID: 426.0528; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0528)
  - Gay USA 11/1/2012, November 1, 2012; ID: 426.0529; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0529)
  - Gay USA 11/8/2012, November 8, 2012; ID: 426.0530; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0530)
  - Gay USA 11/15/2012, November 15, 2012; ID: 426.0531; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0531)
  - Gay USA 11/22/2012 - 13171, November 22, 2012; ID: 426.0532; 1 media elements DVD-R (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0532)
    Original format: DVD-R
  - Gay USA - Opening, Undated; ID: 426.0533; 1 media elements VHS (Box 9, Media ID: 426.0533)
- Series II: Gay USA Collection misc material, April 1980 - October 2006, undated; 2 folders misc. paper material; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Frankie Goes to Hollywood 'Relax'; 1 videocassettes (minidv) Mini DV Head Cleaner
  Scope and Content
  This series contains two folders of random paper material from the Gay USA collection, plus two commercial media items: a mini-DV head cleaning tape, and a U-matic copy of Frankie Goes to Hollywood's 'Relax' music video.
  - Paper material, January 2005 - October 2006, undated; cuid5831 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    This folder contains four sheets of paper. The first is one page of hand written notes, the second is titled "The Earliest Gay Pickets: When, Where, Why" and lists 11 pickets for LGBT causes, the third and four pages are a liscencing agreement between Ann Northrop and WHYY-TV Philadelphia for the use of the film "Gay Pioneers" in the Gay U.S.A. program.
  - Paper material, 1980-1996, undated; cuid6013 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    The folder contains a GCN business card for Gay USA director Louis Maletta, an article ripped out of HX Magazine about Gay Cable Network (written by David Cohen, August 1996), and a letter from a devout Christian that includes a pamphlet called 'The Sissy.'
  - Misc. commercial media, 1 videocassettes (u-matic); 1 videocassettes (minidv) (Box 4)
    This file contains two pieces of commercial media related to Gay USA production material from 2000-2001: one Umatic tape of the music video 'Relax' by the band Frankie Goes to Hollywood, and another a miniDV player head cleaning tape.